

CONTACT

Taman Tun Dr Ismail 60000 Kuala Lumpur MALAYSIA



+6011 1001 3883



✓ aznimr@protonmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/aznimrahman

COURSES

STATISTICAL THINKING FOR DATA SCIENCE & ANALYTICS ColumbiaX 2021(verified cert)

MANAGING ATRIAL
FIBRILLATION COURSE
Stanford University School of
Medicine. 2021 (verified cert)

TYPE 2 DIABETES MANAGEMENT
Stanford University School of
Medicine. 2020 (verified cert)

EDUCATION

BACHELOR DEGREE IN FOOD SCIENCE & NUTRITION

Deakin University, Melbourne
Australia 2010

AWARDS

Awarded Best Sales Representative Malaysia & ASEAN in 2015

Earned excellence recognition for territory expansion and exceeding sales growth by 120%

AZNIM RAHMAN

ABOUT

Highly inquisitive, tenacious and a can-do attitude professional with demonstrated background in the medical device industry. Also comes with clinical knowledge in the operating theatre, relationship-building and business marketing experience desires a position in that capacity. Offering exceptional adaptability in multitasking and shifting priorities with effective analytical, interpersonal and communication skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH VOLUNTEER

VOLUNTEER | 2020 - CURRENT

Volunteering research for London-based independent author & researcher, Dr Kashif Khan

- Assisting in analysing and translating philosophical scriptures from Arabic to English with concise usage of Arabic grammar to ensure accuracy
- Collecting sources on history of ancient civilisations
- Reviewing and discovering associations in modern science, spirituality and global affairs

CLINICAL SALES SPECIALIST

JOHNSON & JOHNSON | 2018 - 2019 | KUALA LUMPUR

- Increased market share of surgical staplers and energy devices under Ethicon General Surgery team
- Provided in-service technical support in the OT to medical personnel in multiple disciplines eg. cardiothoracic and surgical for using company's equipment

CLINICAL SALES SPECIALIST

SMITH & NEPHEW | FEB 2015 - DEC 2016 | KUALA LUMPUR

- Responsible for trouble-shooting, maintaining company's surgical equipment and anticipating device need of surgeons/OT staff during endoscopy procedures eg. ACL, PCL
- Accurately recorded surgical procedure information for invoicing
- Organised and lead arthroscopy & advanced surgical-related workshops for teaching hospitals in territory areas

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

Everyday Essential British Sign Language Level 1 CPD Certified

Operating Theatre In-service Clinical Equipment Support

TECHNICAL

Python Programming

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Power Point

Microsoft Excel

Mac & PC Systems

Social Media

EXTRA

LANGUAGES

English Nativ Malav Nativ

Arabic Intermediat French Beginner

INTERESTS

Philosophical Alchemy Pyramid Mathematics Ancient Civilisations Sacred Geometry Longboarding Vinyasa Yoga

WORK EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

ACCOUNT MANAGER

FROST & SULLIVAN | JAN 2014 - FEB 2015 | KUALA LUMPUR

- Developed trust relationships with a portfolio of major clients in the sectors assigned; energy, automotive, transport
- Prepared regular progress reports and forecasts to both internal & external stakeholders

SALES REPRESENTATIVE | MARKET DEVELOPMENT

MEDTRONIC APAC HQ | SEPT 2012 - OCT 2013 | SINGAPORE

- Expanded market share of dental biologics products to oral maxillo-facial surgeons and periodontists by securing 5 new accounts
- Collaborated with internal marketing team to conduct hands-on demonstrations for workshops in teaching hospitals
- Increased total sales revenue by 150% within 6 months in 2013

PROFESSIONAL SALES REPRESENTATIVE

GLAXOSMITHKLINE | JAN 2011 - JUN 2012 | KUALA LUMPUR

- Responsible for marketing allergy and anti-infective products to public and private hospitals in the allocated territory
- Delivered presentations to hospital departments to further promote product portfolio

REFERENCES

DR KASHIF KHAN, PhD Researcher & Author London

www. quranguide blog. word press. com

YONG CHUNG SHIN

Managing Director
SYS Healthcare
(Pentax Medical subsidiary)
Kuala Lumpur
+6011 2288 2228

TK CHOO

General Manager

DCH Auriga | Kuala Lumpur

Former Smith & Nephew

Country Manager

zkhyechoo@yahoo.com

+6012 488 6826

DR GAN ENG CHENG
MBBS, FRCS, MS Ortho
KPJ DAMANSARA SPECIALIST
Kuala Lumpur
cosmet64@gmail.com
+603 7718 1000 ext 1402
+6012 218 1270